nothing
wound
You carry a
close
been able to
has
reopening,
keeps
a guilt that
you
hard
no matter how
right.
try to make it
before the
years
Seven hundred
cross,
healing
that the
wrote
Isaiah
come
reach would
can't
you
wounds.
else's
someone
through
for
wounded
"But he was
transgressions,
our
for our
bruised
he was
iniquities...
stripes we
his
and with
healed."
are
of a
welts
Stripes the
flogging,
centuries
foresaw
Isaiah
the wounding
Jesus'
on
before it fell
back.
took
Peter
And the apostle
words and laid
Isaiah's
up
at the
Christ
them on
cross:
bare
self
"Who his own
own
his
our sins in
tree...
on the
body
were
stripes ye
whose
by
healed."
does
Peter
And watch what
it.
with
wrote
Isaiah
healed."
"we are
writes
Peter
healed"
"ye were
straight
promise
and points the
listening:
who's
at the one
you.
at
meant to
never
You were
yourself.
it right
make
something you
isn't
The healing
produce
at the
finished
it was
cross,
wounds,
in His own
you.
for
reopening,
keeps
The wound that
closed.
already
has
He
to Him,
Come
it.
receive
and